Resume 2022

NAME Miss Claire M McGonigal

HOME ADDRESS High Hampstead Farm, Petworth, GU28 9EX.

EMAIL mcgonigal.clairem@gmail.com

DATE of Birth 8 December 1987

NATIONALITY British

I have a BSc degree in International Equine & Agricultural Management. Currently working on a data cleansing project for the Cabinet office on the CO Business Intelligence team. My experience and skills gained from previous employment include Teaching, Social Media Management, Data Management, Marketing, Event Coordinator, Personal Assistant, Web Development, Customer Relations, Stock Control, Farm Management and Animal Care. I am house & pet sitting full time throughout the UK. I am studying online to make a career switch into the tech industry. I have previously worked full-time positions in the UK, China

EDUCATION

and Australia.

2012-2015

Royal Agricultural University. BSc degree in International Equine and Agricultural Management

2005 - 2007

University of Glasgow. 2nd Year Marine & Freshwater Biology

1999 - 2005

St. Ninian's High School, Giffnock, East Renfrewshire, Scotland

QUALIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Science in International Equine & Agricultural Management

Harvard CS50 Certificate

EDX Introduction to Linux Certificate

EDX Introduction to Python Certificate

Kaggle Intro to Python & Pandas

Automate the boring stuff with Python, Udemy Certificate

Code First Girls Introduction to Python

Code First Girls Introduction to Data & SQL

EMPLOYMENT

Feb 2022 - Present - Cabinet Officer - <u>Data Officer</u> (contractor)

Working a team of six data quality officers within the CDIO to cleanse, manage and complete various datasets that will inform startegic descisions across the Cabinet Office.

Oct 2018 - Aug 2021 - Whales English - Online English Teacher (contractor)

Mar 2017 - Mar 2018 - Buckland International Education Group - English Teacher

June 2015 – Apr 2016 – Atkin Grant & Lang Gun Club – Club & Event Manager

Managing day to day operations of a shooting ground just outside of London, UK. Organising and running all corporate/private events. In charge of all Marketing, Advertising and Social Media content.

May 2014 – June 2015 – The Riding Club London – Event & Venue Assistant

Working both remotely (whilst during term time at University) and in the central London offices. Organise riding and social events for a private members club. Build an online venue directory by collaborating with other prestigious riding companies and brands in London. Assist with website development and social media management.

Nov 2012 - May 2014- Coffee 1, Cirencester - Supervisor/Barista

Supervisor at a busy coffee chain store in Cirencester, UK. Organise work rotas for staff, cleaning schedules, accounting and ensure day to day operations run smoothly. Fully trained Barista and assisted in training of new staff.

Nov 2011- Aug 2012- The Tearooms- Supervisor/Barmaid

Feb 2011 - Aug 2011 - Rio Tinto- VIP waitress/ Personal assistant (Australia)

June 2010 - Jan 2011 - Spice n Flavor, restaurant – Head Waitress (Australia)

Feb 2010 - Jan 2011- Self-employed - Contract mustering cattle and fencing (Australia)

March 2009 - Feb 2010- Garnet Hollier, Cluen Station-Station-hand/Jillaro (Australia)

Sept 2008 - Jan 2009- GEW Cameron pty ltd.- Machinery operator (Can operate a Bulldozer, Excavator, Scraper and Bobcat on Australian license.)

June 2006 - Aug 2008 - Clarks Shoe Shop - Sales & Qualified Fitter

Feb 2006 - July 2006 - Rascasse Restaurant - Waitress

May 2005 - Sept 2005 - Glasgow Bridge Club - Waitress/Barmaid

2004 - 2006 - Cathcart Castle Golf Club - Waitress

1999 - 2004 - Linn Park Equestrian Centre - Stablehand

REFEREES

Available on request.